Ta-da!
塔-达！
Thank you, thank you.
谢谢，谢谢。
And now,
而现在，
for The Amazing Rickini's next trick...
为神奇的里基尼的下一个魔术...
Oscar said he's gonna have a video game bus at his party.
奥斯卡说他会在他的派对上有一个电子游戏巴士。
And a chocolate fountain with all the dippins.
还有一个巧克力喷泉，配上所有的蘸料。
Speaking of dippins,
说到蘸料，
how about I dippins to this box
我何不蘸入这个盒子
and pull out another trick?
然后拉出另一个魔术呢？
Ooh, I heard karaoke is gonna be there.
哦，我听说那里会有卡拉OK。
You don't like to sing.
你不喜欢唱歌。
No, Carrie Oakie.
不，是Carrie Oakie。
That cute girl from math class.
数学课上那个可爱的女孩。
Come on, guys.
拜托，伙计们。
I need you to pay attention.
我需要你们集中注意力。
Magic's not magic without an audience.
没有观众，魔术就不算魔术。
It's like the light in the fridge:
就像冰箱里的灯：
since there's no audience inside to see it,
因为没有观众在里面看，
do we really know if it turns off when you close the door?
我们真的知道当你关上门时它是否熄灭了吗？
You're right, we don't know.
你说得对，我们不知道。
Or do we? No, we don't.
或者我们真的知道吗？不，我们不知道。
Or do we?
或者我们真的知道吗？
Now observe as I magically separate these rings.
现在请看，我将神奇地分开这些环。
You know, there is gonna be a magician at Oscar's party.
你知道吗，奥斯卡的派对上会有一个魔术师。
Maybe you can ask him how to do that trick
也许你可以问问他怎么做到那个魔术
without the poo-poo face.
不用做出那种‘糟糕’的表情。
First of all,
首先，
this is not my poo-poo face,
这不是我的‘糟糕’表情，
and second,
其次，
I've already got a whole list of questions prepared.
我已经准备了一整串问题。
For example: when will I grow armpit hair?
例如：我什么时候会长腋毛？
This list is for Dad.
这个清单是给爸爸的。
What are those?
那些是什么？
Smoke pellets.
烟雾弹。
[all] Ooh.
哦。
Bup, bup, bup. They're not toys.
不，不，不。它们不是玩具。
They're an important part of a magician's toolbox.
它们是魔术师工具箱中的重要部分。
They create a cloud of smoke to distract the audience.
它们能制造出一团烟雾来分散观众的注意力。
Mom and Dad said I can't use these in the house.
妈妈和爸爸说我不能在家里使用这些。
What if they come in?
如果他们进来怎么办？
They won't.
他们不会的。
They're outside cleaning the gutters.
他们在外面清理排水沟。
We're not gonna leave you hanging.
我们不会让你孤立无援的。
If you get in trouble, we all get in trouble.
如果你遇到麻烦，我们都会遇到麻烦。
Yeah, we stick together. It's the Quad Code.
是的，我们团结一致。这是四人准则。
All for Quad and Quad for All.
全体为四人，四人为全体。
[sighs]
[叹气]
Okay, I'll do it.
好吧，我来做。
[all] Yes!
[所有人] 太好了！
Now stand back and watch The Amazing Rickini
现在站开，看神奇的里奇尼表演
make Squishy Paws disappear.
让软爪消失。
Abracadabra, alakazam.
阿布拉卡达布拉，阿拉卡扎姆。
In a puff of smoke, Squishy will scram!
一阵烟雾中，软爪快跑！
[both coughing]
[两人咳嗽]
Ricky.
瑞奇。
What do you have to say for yourself?
你有什么要为自己辩解的吗？
Ta-da.
塔-达。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
♪ ♪
[man] [whistling melody]
[男人] [吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[man] [whistling melody]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐呐 ♪
Ricky, what were you thinking?
Ricky，你在想什么？
You know you're not allowed to use smoke pellets in the house.
你知道家里不允许使用烟雾弹。
I wasn't using them.
我没有使用它们。
It's all an illusion.
这全都是幻觉。
It wasn't an illusion.
那不是幻觉。
Which means you're in a lot of trouble.
这意味着你会有大麻烦。
- Why do I feel like this is all our fault? - 'Cause it's all our fault.
- 为什么我觉得这都是我们的错？ - 因为就是我们的错。
- Then why are we hiding in here? - 'Cause it's all our fault.
- 那我们为什么躲在这里？ - 因为就是我们的错。
But we told Ricky we'd stick together.
但我们告诉过Ricky我们会团结一致。
- [sighs] Dicky, what do you think? - I think the light just stays on.
- [叹气] Dicky，你怎么看？ - 我认为灯应该一直亮着。
On, on, on, can't see it.
亮着，亮着，亮着，看不见。
On, on, on, on, can't see it.
亮着，亮着，亮着，亮着，看不见。
On, on, on--
继续，继续，继续--
Dicky, focus!
迪基，集中注意力！
What happened to "All for Quad and Quad for All"?
‘为了Quad，Quad为了大家’怎么了？
Yeah, we probably shouldn't bail on him.
是啊，我们可能不应该离开他。
Fine, so let's go tell Mom and Dad
好吧，那我们去告诉爸爸妈妈
whatever punishment Ricky gets, we deserve, too.
无论里基受到什么惩罚，我们也应该承担。
I don't care if Oscar's party is gonna be magical.
我不在乎奥斯卡的派对会不会很神奇。
You're grounded and you're not going.
你被禁足了，你不能去。
[Ricky] What? No way!
[里基]什么？不可能！
On the other hand, why should we all suffer?
另一方面，为什么我们都要受苦？
"Stick together," they said!
他们说，'团结一致'！
"Quad for All," they said!
他们说，'四人一体'！
We've both suffered for our craft, Wondrous Androoni.
我们都为自己的技艺受苦了，神奇的安多尼。
All in the name of magic!
一切都是为了魔法！
Magic's hard.
魔法可不容易。
- Hey, buddy.
嘿，伙计。
Don't "hey, buddy" me.
别'嘿，伙计'我。
Hey, pal.
嘿，朋友。
That's the same as buddy.
那和'伙计'一样。
I can't believe you bailed on me.
我真不敢相信你抛弃了我。
In our defense, it was only because we didn't want to miss out on the party.
我们这么做，只是因为我们不想错过派对。
We were gonna do the right thing,
我们本来打算做正确的事，
but this party is going to be awesome.
但这个派对肯定会很棒。
If you were allowed to go,
如果你被允许去的话，
you'd totally understand our position.
你肯定会理解我们的立场。
So, we're good here?
所以，我们没事了吧？
Oh, we're good.
哦，我们没事了。
Go to your awesome party, backstabbers.
去参加你那棒极了的派对吧，背后捅刀子的人。
I have plenty of awesome stuff happening right here.
我这里也有很多精彩的事情发生。
Like finally organizing my desk.
比如终于整理我的桌子。
Ricky, don't be mad--
Ricky，别生气——
Go! This could take me all night.
走吧！这可能要花我一整晚。
Done!
完成了！
Darn it.
该死。
The video game bus is here!
电子游戏巴士来了！
I get to play the same video games I play at home,
我可以在巴士上玩我在家里玩的电子游戏，
but on a bus!
但在巴士上！
Check it out!
看这个！
You can dip anything in the chocolate fountain.
你可以把任何东西蘸在巧克力喷泉里。
I dipped a taco.
我蘸了一个玉米卷。
Ugh, chocolate meat!
呃，巧克力肉！
Chocolate meat!
巧克力肉！
Man, look at all this magic stuff.
伙计，看看这些神奇的东西。
Ricky would love this.
Ricky会喜欢这个的。
I thought we agreed we weren't gonna talk about Ricky.
我以为我们同意不谈Ricky的。
Hey, where's Ricky?
嘿，Ricky在哪儿？
He couldn't come.
他来不了。
Oh, that's a crying shame. That boy loves magic.
哦，真可惜。那孩子喜欢魔术。
Oh, well. Enjoy the party.
哦，好吧。享受派对吧。
All right, now can we try to have a good time
好吧，我们现在能试着开心点吗
and forget about Ricky?
并且忘记Ricky吗？
Hey, guys. Where's Ricky?
嘿，伙计们。Ricky在哪儿？
[all] He's not here!
他不在！
Wow, that's surprising. That boy loves magic.
哇，这真令人惊讶。那孩子喜欢魔术。
If I had to pick one quad out of all of you that should be here,
如果我必须从你们所有人中选出一个应该在这里的人，
it would be him.
那一定是他。
Oh, well. Have a good time.
哦，好吧。玩得开心。
All right, maybe we should just stay away from people.
好吧，也许我们应该远离人群。
Hey, maybe this will help us forget about Ricky.
嘿，也许这会帮助我们忘记Ricky。
I know what you are thinking.
我知道你在想什么。
[all] Aah!
[所有人] 啊！
All right, the kids are at the party,
好吧，孩子们在派对上，
Ricky's upstairs grounded,
Ricky在楼上被禁足，
and I am done cleaning the gutters.
而我终于清理完了排水沟。
Which means,
这意味着，
it's Tom time.
现在是Tom的时间。
Hmm.
嗯。
How about we make it Tom and Anne time?
我们何不把它变成Tom和Anne的时间？
I'm listening.
我在听。
I'm no longer listening.
我不再听了。
Come on, Tom, we have to clean this place.
来吧，汤姆，我们得打扫这个地方。
Ricky's magic dust is everywhere.
瑞奇的魔法灰尘到处都是。
It's not that bad.
没那么糟糕。
[sighs]
[叹气]
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
Don't worry. It'll settle.
别担心。它会沉淀的。
You know what, fine, but let's at least make this interesting.
你知道吗，好吧，但至少让我们把这个变得有趣些。
If I make this into the fruit basket, you clean up the mess.
如果我把这个变成水果篮，你来清理这个烂摊子。
Sweetie, didn't you learn your lesson from the gutters?
亲爱的，你从水沟里还没学到教训吗？
Every time you don't want to clean,
每次你不想打扫的时候，
you challenge me to some game, I win,
你挑战我玩某个游戏，我赢了，
and you end up having to do it all by yourself.
结果你最后得自己全做了。
What's the matter, Anne?
怎么了，安妮？
You afraid your lucky streak is over?
你怕你的好运到头了？
[laughs]
[笑]
Huh? Huh? Here we go.
嗯？嗯？开始了。
[exhales]
[叹气]
- Hey! - Boom!
- 嘿！ - 砰！
No blocksies!
不许抢！
You never called "no blocksies."
你没喊“不许抢”。
Oh, you want to play street rules?
All right, all right, let's go, Harper.
- First to ten, wins. - I'll spot you nine.
Hey, I have my pride, Anne.
- Pfft. - I'll take eight.
Oh, ho ho, not in my house, Stretch.
You might want to get some ointment,
'cause you're about to get burned.
We're actually really out of ointment,
so next time we're by the pharmacy...
Got it.
明白了。
- Hoo! - Ooh!
哇！
[Nicky] This thing's freaking me out.
这东西让我毛骨悚然。
It looks just like Ricky.
它看起来就像里基。
It's not Ricky, it's just a mind-reading robot.
不是里基，只是个读心机器人。
Ooh, maybe it can read my mind.
哦，也许它能读懂我的心思。
Whoa, he's good.
哇，他真厉害。
He didn't say anything.
他什么都没说。
I wasn't thinking anything.
我什么都没想。
You have to press the button first.
你得先按下按钮。
Let me try.
让我试试。
Do I feel guilty for bailing on Ricky?
我对放里基鸽子感到内疚吗？
Your heart knows the answer.
你的心知道答案。
It does. And I do!
确实如此。我也确实感到内疚！
This is silly. It's just answering randomly.
这太傻了。它只是在随机回答。
Okay, my turn.
好吧，轮到我了。
Oh, Great Cosmo,
哦，伟大的科斯莫，
did we do the wrong thing leaving Ricky at home?
我们把里基留在家里是做错了吗？
Your path soon will become clear.
你的道路很快就会变得清晰。
What do you mean?
你是什么意思？
It's not like we can just sneak him out and bring him over here.
我们不可能偷偷把他带出来带到这里。
Look for a sign.
寻找一个迹象。
Attention.
注意。
In ten minutes, the magic show will begin
十分钟后，魔术表演即将开始
with our very special guest,
与我们非常特别的嘉宾，
The Wondrous Androoni!
神奇的安德鲁尼！
[cheers and applause]
（欢呼和掌声）
Oh, that's Ricky's favorite magician.
哦，那是瑞奇最喜欢的魔术师。
Maybe that's a sign.
也许那是一个迹象。
No, that's not a sign. It's a coincidence.
不，那不是迹象。那是巧合。
[electricity crackles]
[电流噼啪声]
It says "Get Ricky."
上面写着“找Ricky。”
Okay, now that's a sign.
好吧，现在这是个信号。
All right, Anne, playtime's over.
好了，Anne，游戏时间结束了。
It's time to... play.
是时候...玩了。
[blows whistle]
[吹口哨]
This ain't no roller derby.
这可不是什么轮滑比赛。
Hey, you called street rules, Scaredy Shorts.
嘿，你叫了街头规则，胆小短裤。
They should call you Elevator,
他们应该叫你电梯，
cause you're, bing, going down!
因为你，叮，要下去了！
You wish.
你做梦。
- Okay. - Here we go.
好了。
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等，等等。
Should we be doing this here in the living room?
我们真的要在客厅里做这个吗？
I mean, what kind of message does it send to the kids?
我是说，这对孩子们传递了什么信息？
Ah, they'll never see us. Boink!
啊，他们不会看到我们的。
Hey! No, no!
嘿！不，不！
Just going to the bathroom!
只是去洗手间！
[Dicky] Together!
一起！
No time to talk.
没时间聊天。
Ricky!
Ricky！
He made himself disappear.
他让自己消失了。
I'm over here.
我在这儿。
Whoa!
哇！
Wow, he's really improved.
哇，他真的进步了。
Ricky, you are seriously missing out on the best party ever.
Ricky，你真的错过了有史以来最好的派对。
And you came all the way back home just to rub it in?
而你大老远跑回家就是为了炫耀？
Classy.
真有你的。
No, we came to break you out.
不，我们是来救你出去的。
You need to come with us.
你需要跟我们走。
No way. I'm already grounded because of you.
不可能。我已经因为你被禁足了。
And if I do this and get caught,
如果我这么做又被抓到，
I'll be in even more trouble because of you.
我会因为你而惹上更大的麻烦。
The Wondrous Androoni's performing.
神奇的安多尼正在表演。
I'll get my coat.
我去拿外套。
Wait. How are we gonna sneak him out?
等等。我们怎么把他偷偷带出去？
Just meet me at the party.
就在派对上见我。
I'll create the illusion I'm still here.
我会制造出我还在这里的幻觉。
Then make myself...
然后让自己……
disappear.
消失。
You sure you can pull it off?
你确定你能做到吗？
Trust me, I've got a few tricks up my sleeve.
相信我，我还有几招没使出来。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Bring it, chump.
来吧，小菜鸟。
Hey, Mom and Dad,
嘿，爸爸妈妈，
I'm gonna listen to my hour-long crossword puzzle podcast.
我要听我的一个小时的填字游戏播客。
Tonight's the Crossie Awards.
今晚是Crossie奖颁奖典礼。
The competition for the best down word is intense.
最佳纵向单词的竞争非常激烈。
Anyway, no need to check on me for the next hour.
总之，接下来一个小时不用来看我了。
Hey, what's that in the kitchen?
嘿，厨房里那是什么？
Magic is all about...
魔法就是关于...
wonder.
奇迹。
Aah! Aah!
啊！啊！
[applause]
（掌声）
Classic Androoni.
经典的Androoni。
Soak it all in, 'cause in ten minutes,
好好享受吧，因为十分钟后，
your podcast is over and we gotta get you back.
你的播客就结束了，我们得让你回来。
For my next trick,
我的下一个魔术，
I'm going to need a volunteer.
我需要一个志愿者。
You, I guess.
你吧，我想。
Ricky Harper. And I am your biggest fan.
瑞奇·哈珀。我是你的头号粉丝。
By the way, I have a list of questions for you.
顺便说一下，我有一堆问题要问你。
Who wants to see Ricky and his questions
谁想看到瑞奇和他的问题
disappear?
消失？
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
Get ready
准备好
to be filled with wonder!
被惊奇填满吧！
One...
一...
Two...
二...
Three!
三！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
I wonder where he is.
我想知道他在哪里。
Could he be in here?
他会不会在这里面？
I wonder
我想知道
why he's not in there?
为什么他不在那里？
The Wondrous Androoni will be back
神奇的安杜尼将会回来
after a short Wonder-mission.
在短暂的神奇任务之后。
[applause]
[掌声]
He's good.
他很棒。
A little too good.
有点太棒了。
Excuse me, Mr. Androoni--
对不起，安杜尼先生——
Mr. Androoni was my father. Call me Wondrous.
安杜尼先生是我父亲。叫我Wondrous。
Yeah, look, Wondrous, we need our brother back.
是的，听着，Wondrous，我们需要我们的兄弟回来。
I wonder where he is.
我想知道他在哪里。
You lost our brother!
你把我们的兄弟弄丢了！
The Wondrous Androoni has never lost anyone...
Wondrous Androoni从未丢失过任何人……
until now.
直到现在。
Magic's hard.
魔法很难。
Guys, we have five minutes to get Ricky back to the house.
伙计们，我们还有五分钟要把Ricky带回家。
But he's in the magic netherworld.
但他现在在魔法异界。
He's gotta be around here somewhere.
他一定就在这附近的某个地方。
You two stay here and look for him.
你们两个留在这里找他。
I'm gonna go home and stall Mom and Dad.
我要回家去拖延一下爸妈。
How are you gonna do that?
你怎么拖延他们？
The answer is right in front of you.
答案就在你眼前。
I think I know someone who can help.
我想我知道谁能帮忙。
Who?
谁？
- Okay. - Okay.
好的。
- All tied up. - Okay.
Next basket wins.
下一个篮子赢。
Got it. Let's go.
明白了，我们走。
Yeah.
是的。
Ooh. Hoo. Okay.
哦，呼。好的。
- Ho! - No, no! Oh!
哇！不，不！哦！
Oh!
哦！
My vase!
我的花瓶！
First of all, it's vahhz.
首先，是花瓶（vase）。
Oh!
哦！
And secondly...
其次...
Boom! Tomahawk!
嘭！战斧式扣篮！
Yeah!
耶！
I can't believe you broke my vase just so you could win!
我真不敢相信你为了赢竟然打碎了我的花瓶！
Hey, guys!
嘿，伙计们！
Hey. You're back again?
嘿。你又回来了？
Crazy line for the bathroom. Gotta go!
厕所排长队。得赶紧走了！
You know, she does have your tiny bladder.
你知道的，她确实有你那种小膀胱。
Come on, Cosmo.
拜托，科斯莫。
I can't believe you cheated.
我真不敢相信你作弊了。
I did not. I broke your vahhz by accident.
我没有。我是不小心打碎了你的花瓶。
I can tell you're lying by that smirk on your...fahhz.
我能看出你在撒谎，从你那得意的...花瓶。
- Accident. - Purpose!
- 意外。 - 故意！
La la la la la!
啦啦啦啦啦！
[footsteps approaching]
[脚步声接近]
Uh-oh.
哎呀。
Hey, sweetie, you awake?
嘿，宝贝，你醒着吗？
Oh, good. How was your podcast?
哦，太好了。你的播客怎么样？
Did all your favorite words win?
你最喜欢的那些词都赢了吗？
Honey?
亲爱的？
I know you're still mad about the party,
我知道你还对派对的事生气，
but you need to talk to me.
但你需要跟我谈谈。
I know what you're thinking.
我知道你在想什么。
Wait, really? Is it that obvious?
等等，真的吗？有这么明显吗？
Your mind is an open book.
你的心思就像一本打开的书。
Oh, huh. I guess it is.
哦，嗯。我想是的。
You know, I just wanted him to help clean.
你知道，我只是想让他帮忙打扫。
And then we got into this crazy game,
然后我们就玩了这个疯狂的游戏，
and I mean, I was dominating him,
我的意思是，我完全压制了他，
but still, I said he cheated, and maybe he didn't.
但尽管如此，我说他作弊了，也许他并没有。
And now I don't know what to do.
现在我不知道该怎么办了。
Your heart knows the answer.
你的心知道答案。
You know what, you're right.
你知道吗，你说得对。
I'm sure he didn't do it on purpose.
我相信他不是故意的。
Thank you, sweetie.
谢谢你，亲爱的。
I'm so glad we had this conversation.
我很高兴我们进行了这次对话。
[Cosmo] Your future is bright.
你的未来一片光明。
I love that positive attitude.
我喜欢这种积极的态度。
[whispers] That's why you're my favorite.
这就是你成为我的最爱的原因。
[magician's music]
魔术师的音乐
Ricky's gotta be in here somewhere.
里基一定在这儿的某个地方。
Ricky!
里基！
Maybe he's in this box.
也许他在这个箱子里。
♪ ♪
Ugh. I'll look out here.
呃，我在这边找找。
♪ ♪
Watch the hair.
注意头发。
[crash]
[碰撞声]
[cat meows]
[猫叫]
[knock on door]
[敲门声]
[Tom] Rickster? It's Dad.
Rickster？是爸爸。
Hey, you still mad about missing the party?
嘿，你还在为错过了派对生气吗？
- I know what you are thinking.
我知道你在想什么。
Really?
真的吗？
- Your mind is an
你的心思就像
[slowing down] open...
一本...
book.
打开的书。
Whoa, what's going on there?
哇，那里发生了什么？
Sounds like you're winding down.
听起来你正在放松。
Well, it's been a rough day for everybody.
嗯，今天对每个人来说都很艰难。
Especially your mom.
特别是你妈妈。
I beat her fair and square
我公平地赢了她
and she's taking it pretty hard.
而且她对此感到相当难过。
- Answer... heart...knows.
答案...心...知道。
Wait, something's wrong here.
等等，这里有问题。
You're not Ricky.
你不是Ricky。
You're super-sleepy Ricky.
你是超级困的Ricky。
But you're right.
但你是对的。
Answer heart does know.
答案，心确实知道。
You are one smart kid.
你真是个聪明的孩子。
I'm gonna apologize to your mother.
我要向你妈妈道歉。
Thank you, Ricky.
谢谢你，Ricky。
[whispers] That's why you're my favorite.
[低语] 这就是你是我最喜欢的理由。
And now for my grand finale!
现在轮到我的压轴大戏了！
Oscar, you remember I made your little friend disappear.
奥斯卡，你记得我让你的小朋友们消失了。
Well, let's see if I can bring him back!
那么，看看我能否把他们带回来！
[grunting]
[咕哝声]
Voila!
瞧！
Apparently not.
显然没有。
And the Wondrous Androoni
神奇的安多尼
will leave you wondering.
会让你疑惑不解。
Good night, everyone!
大家晚安！
I wonder how he keeps getting work.
我想知道他是怎么一直找到工作的。
Tom.
汤姆。
Anne.
安妮。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I know you didn't break my vase on purpose.
我知道你不是故意打碎我的花瓶的。
Actually, I may have broken the vase on purpose a little.
实际上，我可能有点故意打碎了花瓶。
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I just hate always losing to you.
我只是讨厌总是输给你。
Yeah, I guess I don't make it easy.
是啊，我想我也没让你轻松。
Well, it doesn't help when you call me
嗯，当你叫我
Little Tommy Loserpants.
小汤米输裤子。
Even?
甚至？
[sighs] Even.
甚至。
Hmm.
嗯。
Okay.
好吧。
- I'll get the brooms. - Okay.
我去拿扫帚。
Don't even.
别提了。
Man that punch goes right through ya!
那一拳直击要害！
I gotta stick with my bathroom buddy.
我得和我的浴室伙伴在一起。
Wait, something's not right.
等等，有什么不对劲。
Ricky is Nicky's bathroom buddy.
Ricky是Nicky的浴室伙伴。
We can't find Ricky!
我们找不到Ricky了！
He's in the magic netherworld!
他在魔法异界！
What?
什么？
[Tom] Kids?
[Tom]孩子们？
Well, at least we still have Cosmo.
嗯，至少我们还有Cosmo。
[Cosmo crashes]
[Cosmo摔倒]
[all] Ooh!
[所有人]哦！
[Tom] Is everything okay?
[Tom]一切都好吗？
We have to make it look like Ricky's sleeping.
我们得让Ricky看起来像在睡觉。
[Anne] Kids?
孩子们？
What's going on up here?
楼上发生什么事了？
Shh, Ricky's sleeping.
嘘，Ricky在睡觉。
Yeah. And he asked us not to disturb him.
是的。他让我们不要打扰他。
No, he didn't, because he's sleeping.
不，他没有，因为他正在睡觉。
What are you kids up to?
你们这些孩子在搞什么鬼？
No, it's okay.
不，没关系。
You don't have to come in here.
你们不用进来。
See? Ricky's sleeping.
看吧？Ricky在睡觉。
[all] Aah!
啊！
There he is!
他在那儿！
Exactly where we thought he'd be.
正是我们预料他会待的地方。
What's going on?
发生什么事了？
Oh, I'm so sorry, kids.
哦，孩子们，真是抱歉。
- We'll let you get back to sleep, buddy. - Yeah.
我们会让你继续睡觉的，伙计。
- Dude, how'd you get back in here?
是啊。
A good magician never reveals his secrets.
哥们，你是怎么回到这里的？
Dad left the ladder out
一个好魔术师永远不会透露他的秘密。
when he was cleaning the gutters, didn't he?
爸爸清理排水沟时把梯子留在外面了，对吧？
Yeah, pretty much.
是啊，差不多。
Thanks for making me go to that party and covering for me.
谢谢你让我去参加那个派对并帮我打掩护。
Hey, it's the Quad Code.
嘿，这是四人组的暗号。
All for Quad...
一切为了四人组...
[all] And Quad for All!
[所有人] 四人组为了所有人！
All right, I'll take Cosmo back to the party and we will be--
好吧，我会带Cosmo回到派对，我们会...
Hey!
嘿！
So, Ricky.
那么，Ricky。
Josie came by to give you this.
Josie过来给你这个。
Apparently you left it in the vanishing cabinet
显然你把它落在Oscar派对上的消失柜里了。
at Oscar's party.
我简直不敢相信你偷偷溜出去了。
I can't believe you snuck out.
Now you're really grounded.
现在你真的被禁足了。
What do you have to say for yourself?
你有什么要为自己辩解的吗？
I'm sorry.
对不起。
I shouldn't have snuck out to that party.
我不应该偷偷溜出去参加那个派对。
No, it was our fault.
不，那是我们的错。
Yeah, we convinced him to sneak out.
是的，是我们说服他偷偷溜出去的。
Why would you do that?
你们为什么要这么做？
Because we also convinced him to throw the smoke pellets.
因为我们还说服他扔了烟雾弹。
And then let him get in trouble for it.
然后让他因此惹上麻烦。
So if you're gonna punish Ricky,
所以如果你们要惩罚Ricky，
you have to punish all of us.
你们也得惩罚我们所有人。
[both] Yeah.
对。
All right.
好吧。
But before you do,
但在你们这么做之前，
I have one question for you.
我有一个问题要问你们。
Which one of us is your favorite?
我们当中谁是你们最喜欢的？
That's silly. We don't have favorites.
这很傻。我们没有最喜欢的。
I was under Ricky's bed the whole time.
我整个时间都躲在Ricky的床底下。
- Parent huddle. - Yep.
家长会议。 - 是的。
[clears throat]
[清喉咙]
[whispering]
[低声说话]
- You're all free to go. - Yep.
- 你们都可以走了。- 是的。
- Whoo! - Yeah!
- 哇！- 耶！
- Whoo! - All right!
- 哇！- 好极了！
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
[whistling melody]
[口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
[音乐]
♪ Yeah! ♪
[音乐] - 耶！
♪
[音乐]
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪
- ♪
♪